Finding Aid for the Theodore Payne Papers LSC.2368
UCLA Library Special Collections
- Nursery catalogs, 1895-1969; Series 9.
  - Ornamental Tree Vines and Shrubs, 1938 February 15; Del Amo Nurseries (Box 90)
  - Ornamental Tree Vines and Shrubs, 1940 January; Del Amo Nurseries (Box 90)
  - Garden, Field, Flower and Tree Seeds, Bulbs, Etc., 1893; Denham's (Box 90)
  - Wholesale Contract Price List, 1958; Denholm Seed Company (Box 90)
    Crop 1958
  - Wholesale Contract Price List, 1960; Denholm Seed Company (Box 90)
    Crop 1960
  - Wholesale Contract Price List, 1961; Denholm Seed Company (Box 90)
    Crop 1961
  - Wholesale Contract Price List, 1962; Denholm Seed Company (Box 90)
    Crop 1962
  - Wholesale Contract Price List, 1963; Denholm Seed Company (Box 90)
    Crop 1963
  - Seeds, Bulbs, Plants, 1913 Spring; Diener, Richard & Co. (Box 90)
  - Catalog, 1937; Diener, Richard & Co. (Box 90)
  - Wholesale & Retail, 1957 November; Edmunds, L.L. (Box 90)
    Loose sheets
  - Catalogue, 1935; Evans Gardens (Box 91)
  - Catalogue, 1942 Spring; Evans & Reeves Nurseries (Box 91)
  - California Horticulture: The Fruit Grower's Guide, undated; Fancher Creek Nurseries (Box 91)
  - Catalogue of Seeds, 1894-1895; Germain Fruit Co. (Box 91)
  - Catalogue of Seeds, 1896-1897; Germain Fruit Co. (Box 91)
  - Catalogue of Seeds, 1898-1899; Germain Fruit Co. (Box 91)
  - Catalogue of Seeds, 1899-1900; Germain Fruit Co. (Box 91)
  - Catalogue of Seeds, 1900; Germain Fruit Co. (Box 91)
  - California Wild Flower Seeds, 1932; Germain's (Box 91)
  - California Wild Flower Seeds, 1932; Germain's (Box 91)
  - Bulbs, 1900 Autumn; Germain Seed & Plant Co. (Box 91)
  - Bulbs, 1901 Autumn; Germain Seed & Plant Co. (Box 91)
  - Bulbs, 1902 Autumn; Germain Seed & Plant Co. (Box 91)
  - Catalog, 1902; Germain Seed & Plant Co. (Box 91)
  - Theodore Payne Private / Catalog, 1902; Germain Seed & Plant Co. (Box 91)
  - Catalog, 1903; Germain Seed & Plant Co. (Box 91)
  - Theodore Payne Private / Catalog, 1903; Germain Seed & Plant Co. (Box 91)
  - Catalog, 1909; Germain Seed & Plant Co. (Box 91)
  - Catalog, 1909; Germain Seed & Plant Co. (Box 91)
  - Wholesale Prices, 1932 Fall; Germain's Bulbs (Box 91)
  - Semillas Y Plantas, undated; Germain Seed Co. (en Espanol) (Box 91)
  - Semillas de Hortalizas, Flores, Etc., 1894-1895; Germain Seed Co. (en Espanol) (Box 91)
  - Semillas de Hortalizas, Flores, Etc., 1894-1895; Germain Seed Co. (en Espanol) (Box 91)
  - Ornamental Trees and Shrubbery, undated; Golden State Plant and Floral Co. (Box 91)
  - Hotel Green Pasadena, 1917 March 29-31; Hanson, A.E. Plants (Box 91)
  - Garden Book & Seed Catalog, 1925; Harris Seed Co. (Box 91)
  - Stock List, undated; Horne's, S.R. Nurseries (Box 92)
  - Roggli's Swiss Giants, undated; Herrmann's Perennial Garden (Box 92)
  - Bulbs for Pots and Spring Planting in the Garden, 1958 Spring; Houdyshel, Cecil (Box 92)
  - Paul J. Howard Horticulture Establishment, 1933 (Box 92)
  - Roses for 1941: From The Garden of a Thousand Roses, Paul J. Howard's California Flowerland (Box 92)
  - Wholesale Price List, 1942 January 15; Howard Rose Company (Box 92)
  - Catalogue and Price List, 1900; Howard & Smith Nurserymen (Box 92)
  - 1954 Picturama of Plants You Can Sell, Hummel's Exotic Gardens (Box 92)
  - Descriptive Price List of Perennials, undated; Jannoch Nurseries (Box 92)
  - Johnson Water Gardens: Cactus, Waterlilies, Succulents, 1936; Johnson, Harry (Box 92)
  - Johnson Water Gardens: Cactus, Waterlilies, Succulents, 1937; Johnson, Harry (Box 92)
  - A Treatise on Fruit Growing: Deciduous and Citrus Fruits, Grape Vines and Eucalyptus, 1913; Kirkman Nurseries (Box 92)
  - Specialties in Pine Palms and California Natives, 1951 Fall; La Tuna Nursery (Box 92)
  - Wholesale Price List, undated; Lester Rose Gardens, The (Box 92)
  - Wholesale Catalogue of Pacific Coast Tree Seeds, 1934-1935; Manning Seed Company, The (Box 92)
  - Novelty Flowering Eucalyptus, undated; L.B. Merrick Nurseries (Box 92)
  - Wholesale Price List, 1959 Fall-1960 Spring; L.B. Merrick Nurseries (Box 92)
  - Wholesale Price List, 1959 Fall-1960 Spring; L.B. Merrick Nurseries (Box 92)
  - Wholesale Price List, 1961 Fall-1962 Spring; L.B. Merrick Nurseries (Box 92)
  - Wholesale Seeds, 1961-1962; Mistletoe Sales (Box 92)
  - Monrovia Nursery Company, undated (Box 92)
  - 1939-40 Wholesale Price List, 1939-1940; Monrovia Nursery Co. (Box 92)
  - Descriptive Price List of New Introductions and other desirable Plants, 1909 November; Montarioso Nursery (Box 92)
  - Monterey Eucalyptus Nursery and Eucalyptus Land Agency, undated; Monterey Eucalyptus Nursery - G.W. Wallace (Box 92)
  - Special Collections 1968-69, 1968-1969; Moore Miniature Roses - Sequoia Nursery (Box 92)
  - California Wild Flowers Collected by Mrs. Edith Murphey, undated; Murphey, Edith (Box 92)
  - Wholesale List, undated; Pacific Coast Laboratory and Wild Plant Improvement Gardens (Box 92)
  - Ground Cover Guide, undated; Perry's Plants: Wholesale Growers of Transplants (Box 92)
  - Spring & Summer 1960 Retail List, 1960 Spring and Summer; Perry's Plants: Wholesale Growers of Transplants (Box 92)
  - Descriptive List of Ground Cover Plants, undated; Perry's Plants: Wholesale Growers of Transplants (Box 92)
  - Pioneer Nursery of Monrovia 1876 to 1927, 1876-1927; Pioneer Nursery of Monrovia (Box 92)
  - Catalogue and Price List, undated; Pioneer Nursery of Monrovia (Box 92)
  - Pioneer Nursery of Monrovia 1876 to 1927, 1876-1927; Pioneer Nursery of Monrovia (Box 92)
  - Descriptive, Illustrated Price Catalog, 1923; Pioneer Nursery of Monrovia (Box 92)
  - Catalogue and Price List, undated; Pioneer Nursery of Monrovia (Box 92)
  - Wholesale Price List of Californian Bulbs, 1898; Purdy, Carl (Box 92)
  - Wholesale Price List of Californian Bulbs and Burbank's Hybrid Lilies, 1905; Purdy, Carl (Box 92)
  - Perennial Plants from All Over the World: Rock Plants and Floral Novelties, 1927 Fall-1928 Spring; Purdy, Carl (Box 92)
  - California's Choicest Bulbs, 1928 Fall-1929 Spring; Purdy, Carl (Box 92)
  - Perennial Plants from All Over the World: Rock Plants and Floral Novelties, 1929 Fall-1929 Spring; Purdy, Carl (Box 92)
  - Perennial Plants from All Over the World: Rock Plants and Floral Novelties, 1930 Fall-1931 Spring; Purdy, Carl (Box 92)
  - Combined Offerings of Californian and Other West American Bulbs and Plants: Rock Garden and Alpine Plants, Unusual Perennials, 1933 Fall-1934 Spring; Purdy, Carl (Box 92)
  - Combined Offerings of Californian and Other West American Bulbs and Plants: Rock Garden and Alpine Plants, Unusual Perennials, 1934 Fall-1935 Spring; Purdy, Carl (Box 92)
  - Combined Offerings of Californian and Other West American Bulbs and Plants: Hardy Perennials, Rock Garden and Alpine Plants, 1935 Fall-1936 Spring; Purdy, Carl (Box 92)
  - Combined Offerings of Californian and Other West American Bulbs and Plants: Hardy Perennials and Rock Garden Plants, 1936 Fall-1937 Spring; Purdy, Carl (Box 92)
  - Combined Offerings of Californian and Other West American Bulbs and Plants, 1937 Fall-1938 Spring; Purdy, Carl (Box 92)
  - Combined Offerings of Californian and Other West American Bulbs and Plants, 1939 Fall-1940 Spring; Purdy, Carl (Box 92)
  - Combined Offerings of Californian and Other West American Bulbs and Plants, 1940 Fall-1941 Spring; Purdy, Carl (Box 92)
  - Combined Offerings of Californian and Other West American Bulbs and Plants, 1942 Fall-1943 Spring; Purdy, Carl (Box 92)
  - Wholesale Pricelist of California Bulbs, 1932 March 10; Purdy, Carl (Box 93)
  - California and Other Western America Bulbs and Plants, 1944 Fall-1945 Spring; Purdy, Carl (Box 93)
  - California and Other Western America Bulbs and Plants, 1946 Fall-1947 Spring; Purdy, Carl (Box 93)
  - California and Other Western America Bulbs and Plants, 1946 Fall-1947 Spring; Purdy, Carl (Box 93)
  - California and Other Western America Bulbs and Plants, 1947 Fall-1948 Spring; Purdy, Carl (Box 93)
  - California and Other Western America Bulbs and Plants, 1947 Fall-1948 Spring; Purdy, Carl (Box 93)
  - California and Other Western America Bulbs and Plants, 1948 Fall-1949 Spring; Purdy, Carl (Box 93)
  - California and Other Western America Bulbs and Plants, 1949 Fall-1950 Spring; Purdy, Carl (Box 93)
  - California and Other Western America Bulbs and Plants, 1950 Fall-1951 Spring; Purdy, Carl (Box 93)
  - Purdy's Bulbs for Fall Planting, undated; Purdy, Carl (Box 93)
  - California's Choicest Bulbs, 1930 Fall-1931 Spring; Purdy, Carl (Box 93)
  - Unusual Seeds, undated; Ransom Seed Co. (Box 93)
  - Grow Christmas Trees for Profit!, undated; Ransom Seed Co. (Box 93)
  - Essential Aromatics, undated; Ritter & Co. (Box 93)
  - Catalog, 1956-1957; Robin, Clyde (Box 93)
  - Catalog, 1959-1962; Robin, Clyde (Box 93)
  - Catalog, 1962-1964; Robin, Clyde (Box 93)
  - California Nursery Company, undated; Roeding, George C. (Box 93)
  - Roeding's Practicle Planter's Guide: The Result of Thirty Years Experince in California Horticulture, 1915; Roeding, George C. (Box 93)
  - California Wild Flower Seeds: The World's Largest Collection of Wild Flower Seeds, undated; Rowntree, Lester (Box 93)
  - California Wild Flower Seeds: The World's Largest Collection of Wild Flower Seeds, undated; Rowntree, Lester (Box 93)
  - California Wild Flower Seeds, undated; Rowntree, Lester (Box 93)
    List No. 4
  - California Wild Flower Seeds, undated; Rowntree, Lester (Box 93)
    List No. 5
  - California Wild Flower Seeds, undated; Rowntree, Lester (Box 93)
    Supplement to List No. 7
  - California Wild Flower Seeds: Seed of Rock Plants, Hardy Perennials, Annuals, Bulbs, Shrubs, undated; Rowntree, Lester (Box 93)
  - California Wild Flower Seeds: Seed of Rock Plants, Hardy Perennials, Annuals, Bulbs, Shrubs, undated; Rowntree, Lester (Box 93)
  - Catalog of the Edward H. Rust Nurseries, undated; Rust, Edward H. (Box 93)
  - F. Rynveld & Sons, 1932 September; Rynveld, F. (Box 93)
  - Price List of the Santa Barbara Nursery Co., 1910-1911; Santa Barbara Nursery Co. (Box 93)
  - Condensed Catalogue and Price List, 1905 March 22; Southern California Acclimatizing Association (Box 93)
  - Catalogue of Rare Water Lilies and Other Choice Aquatic Plants, 1907-1908; Sturtevant, Edmund D. (Box 93)
  - Catalogue of Rare Water Lilies and Other Choice Aquatic Plants, 1907-1908; Sturtevant, Edmund D. (Box 93)
  - Annual Catalogue of Plants and Trees, undated; Sycamore Grove Nurseries (Box 93)
  - Descriptive Catalogue of Ornamental Stock, undated; Sycamore Grove Nurseries (Box 93)
  - California Seeds and Plants: F. Gilman Taylor Seed Co., 1906; Taylor, F. Gilman (Box 93)
  - San Dimas Citrus Nurseries, 1903-1904; Teague, R.M. (Box 93)
  - Roses of Yesterday, 1947; The Lester Rose Gardens (Box 93)
  - Theodosia B. Shepherd Company, undated; Theodosia B. Shepherd Company. (Box 93)
  - Wholesale Price List: Large Growers of Small Seed, undated; Theodosia B. Shepherd Company. (Box 93)
  - Descriptive Catalogue: Rare Plants Choice Flower Seeds Cacti and Succulents, 1914; Theodosia B. Shepherd Company. (Box 93)
  - Tetley Nurseries: Palms for California, undated; Tetley Nurseries (Box 94)
  - Tetley Nurseries: Palms for California, undated; Tetley Nurseries (Box 94)
  - Tuttle Brothers Nurseries: Roses for 1940, Tuttle Brothers (Box 94)
  - Tuttle Brothers Nurseries: Perennial Flowering Plants, undated; Tuttle Brothers (Box 94)
  - Tuttle Brothers Nurseries: Roses 1938-1939, Tuttle Brothers (Box 94)
  - Tuttle Bros. Nurseries: 1953 Catalog, Tuttle Brothers (Box 94)
  - Tydee Bulb Gardens: Growers of Fine Bulbs, 1932; Tydee Bulb Gardens (Box 94)
  - Catalog & Culture, 1936; Vetterle & Reinelt: Hybridizing Gardens (Box 94)
  - 1960 Catalogue, Vetterle & Reinelt: Hybridizing Gardens (Box 94)
  - 1962 Catalogue, Vetterle & Reinelt: Hybridizing Gardens (Box 94)
  - Trade Price List, 1938-1939; Wagner Nurseries (Box 94)
  - Trade Price List, 1939-1940; Wagner Nurseries (Box 94)
  - Trade Price List, 1940-1941; Wagner Nurseries (Box 94)
  - Wholesale Contract and Descriptive Trade List, 1957; Waller Flowerseed Company (Box 94)
  - Wholesale Contract and Descriptive Trade List, 1958; Waller Flowerseed Company (Box 94)
  - Waller Flowerseed Company, 1961 (Box 94)
  - Waller Flowerseed Company, 1962-1963 (Box 94)
  - Tropical Fruits for California, 1913 April; West India Gardens: Importers and Growers of Subtropical Plants and Trees (Box 94)
  - Book of Gardening, 1921; Winsel-Gibbs Seed Company (Box 94)
  - Winsel's Annual Garden Calendar, 1909; Winsel, Charles (Box 94)
  - Carnations Pinks and Dianthus, 1956; Allwood Bros, Ltd. (Box 95)
  - Nursery Trade List, 1912 Autumn and 1913 Spring; Barbier & Co. (Successors) (Box 95)
  - Barr's Seed Guide, 1927; Barr & Sons (Box 95)
  - Bath's Select Vegetable and Flower Seeds Including Sweet Peas, 1934 January; Bath, R.H. Ltd. (Box 95)
  - Bath's Special Trade Offer of Bulbs, 1926; Bath, R.H. Ltd. (Box 95)
  - Specialists in Seed Pockets and Labels: Seed Bulb & Nursery Catalogues, undated; Blake & Mackenzie Ltd. (Box 95)
  - Specialists in Seed Pockets and Labels: Seed Bulb & Nursery Catalogues, 1928-1929; Blake & Mackenzie Ltd. (Box 95)
  - Horticultural Printing Works, Seed Pocket & Label Factory, 1915-1917; Blake & Mackenzie Ltd. (Box 95)
  - Rare Alpine Seeds, 1938; Boothman, Stuart (Box 95)
  - Garden & Lawn, 1928; Carters Tested Seeds (Box 95)
  - Wholesale Seed Catalogue, 1929 January 30; Carter, J., Dunnett, & Beale (Box 95)
  - New Cactus Dahlias for 1898, Cheal, J. & Sons (Box 95)
  - Supplementary Catalogue of Dahlias, 1903; Cheal, J. & Sons (Box 95)
  - Descriptive Catalogue of Hardy Herbaceous and Choice Florists' Flowers, 1903; Cheal, J. & Sons (Box 95)
  - Descriptive Catalogue of Fruit Trees, undated; Cheal, J. & Sons (Box 95)
  - Descriptive Catalogue of Fruit Trees, undated; Cheal, J. & Sons (Box 95)
  - Catalogue of Ornamental Trees and Shrubs, undated; Cheal, J. & Sons (Box 95)
  - Descriptive Catalogue of Fruit Trees, undated; Cheal, J. & Sons (Box 95)
  - Supplementary Catalogue of Dahlias, 1897 Autumn and 1898 Spring; Cheal, J. & Sons (Box 95)
  - Supplementary Catalogue of Dahlias, 1903; Cheal, J. & Sons (Box 95)
  - Descriptive Catalogue of Hardy Herbaceous and Choice Florists' Flowers, undated; Cheal, J. & Sons (Box 96)
  - Supplementary Catalogue of Dahlias, 1903; Cheal, J. & Sons (Box 96)
  - Catalogue of Ornamental Trees and Shrubs, undated; Cheal, J. & Sons (Box 96)
  - Descriptive Catalogue of Hardy Herbaceous, Alpine, Rock and Border Plants, undated; Cheal, J. & Sons (Box 96)
  - Descriptive Catalog of Roses, undated; Cheal, J. & Sons, Crawley (Box 96)
  - Selected Novelties in Vegetable Seeds, undated; Cheal, J. & Sons (Box 96)
  - Trade Price List of Horticultural Sundries, undated; Corry & Co Ltd. (Box 96)
  - Catalog of Selected Trees, Shrubs and Plants, 1941 Spring- 1942 Spring; Hillier & Sons (Box 96)
  - Hobbies Garden Guide, 1903; Hobbies (Box 96)
  - Hobbies Garden Guide, 1903; Hobbies (Box 96)
  - General Trade Catalogue, 1929; Hurst & Son (Box 96)
  - General Trade Catalogue, 1938; Hurst & Son (Box 96)
  - Flower Seeds for Summer, Autumn and Present Sowing, 1938; Hurst & Son (Box 96)
  - Special Offer of Flower Seeds, 1938 Autumn; Hurst & Son (Box 96)
  - General Trade Catalogue, 1960; Hurst & Son Ltd. (Box 96)
  - General Trade Catalogue, 1961; Hurst & Son Ltd. (Box 96)
  - Wholesale Seed Catalogue, 1931; Johnson, W.W. & Son Ltd (Box 96)
  - Wholesale Seed Catalogue, 1929; Johnson, W.W. & Son Ltd (Box 96)
  - Cover Missing*, 1906 July 6; Dobbie & Co. Rothesay (Box 96)
  - Wholesale Catalogue for the Whole Year, 1912; Kelway & Son (Box 97)
  - Catalogue of Dahlias, &C., 1903; Mortimer, S. (Box 97)
  - Flower & Vegetable Seed Book, 1959; Ryders' (Box 97)
  - Catalogue of Alpine and Herbaceous Plants, undated; Six Hills Seeds (Box 97)
  - Trade List of Nursery Stock, 1926 Autumn-1927 Spring; Smith, James (Box 97)
  - Sutton's Bulbs, 1903; Sutton's (Box 97)
  - Catalogue of Choice Flower and Vegetable Seeds, undated; Thompson & Morgan (Box 97)
    67th Annual Issue
  - Catalogue of Choice Flower and Vegetable Seeds, 1938; Thompson & Morgan (Box 97)
    83rd Annual Issue
  - Nursery Trade List, 1913 Autumn and 1914 Spring; Transon Brothers' and D. Dauvesse's (Box 97)
  - Novelties, 1908-1909; Veitch, James & Sons Ltd. (Box 97)
  - Wallace's Irises, undated; R. Wallace & Co., Ltd. (Box 97)
  - Wallace's Bulbs, 1923 September; Wallace's (Box 97)
  - Wallace's Bulbs, 1924 September; Wallace's (Box 97)
  - What's in a Name?, 1921; Watkins & Simpson, Limited (Box 97)
  - Foreign and Colonial Wholesale Catalogue of Vegetable & Flower Seeds, 1927 Season (Box 97)
  - Wholesale Catalogue of Vegetable and Flower Seeds, 1940; Watkins & Simpson, Limited (Box 97)
    1940 Overseas War-time Edition
  - Wholesale Catalogue of Flower Seeds for Export, 1941 Season; Watkins & Simpson, Limited (Box 97)
  - A Catalogue of Dahlias, undated; West, J.T. (Box 97)
  - General Trade Catalogue of Vegetable, Agricultural, Flower, Tree and Other Seeds, 1912-1913; Benary, Ernst (Box 98)
  - Special Offer of Vegetable Seeds for Early Sowing, 1914 September 12; Benary, Ernst (Box 98)
  - General Trade Catalogue, 1925-1926; Benary, Ernst (Box 98)
  - Wholesale Price List of Flower Seeds, 1952-1953; Benary, Ernst (Box 98)
  - Wholesale Price List of Flower Seeds, 1953-1954; Benary, Ernst (Box 98)
  - Ernst Benary's Flower Seeds, 1959-1960; Benary, Ernst (Box 98)
  - Ernst Benary Hann. Muenden Flower Seeds, 1960-1961; Benary, Ernst (Box 98)
  - Contract Price List Flower Seeds, 1961; Benary, Ernst (Box 98)
  - Ernst Benary Flower Seeds, 1962-1963; Benary, Ernst (Box 98)
  - Trade Catalogue For Seeds of Cacti and other Succulents, 1954 February; Blossfeld, Robert (Box 98)
  - Verlagskatalog Botanik, 1811-1933; Botanik (Box 98)
  - Wholesale-Catalogue with Business Terms of Flower and Vegetable Seeds, 1925-1926; Gebruder Dippe A.-G. (Box 98)
  - Wholesale-Catalogue with Business Terms of Flower and Vegetable Seeds, 1930-1931; Gebruder Dippe A.-G. (Box 98)
  - Gemuse- und Blumensamen - Auslands - Katalog Catalogue of choice flower and vegetable seeds, 1937-1938; Gebruder Dippe A.-G. (Box 98)
  - Exportkatalog fur Gemuse- und Blumensaatgut aus der Deutschen Demokratischen Republik, undated; Gemuse- und Blumensaatgut (Box 98)
  - Exportkatalog fur Gemuse- und Blumensamen, undated; Saat- und Pflanzgut (Box 98)
  - Seed Growing Establishment Vegetable, Flower and Farm Seeds, 1911-1912; Grashoff, Martin (Box 98)
  - Forest-Seed-House, 1936 September; Grunwald & Co. (Box 98)
  - Catalogue General de graines et plantes de Haag & Schmidt Horticulteures & Marchands grainiers a Erfurt (Allemagne), 1914; Haage & Schmidt (Box 98)
  - Seed Growers and Nurserymen Trade Seed-Catalogue, 1914-1915; Haage & Schmidt (Box 99)
  - Seed Growers and Nurserymen Trade Seed-Catalogue, 1914-1915; Haage & Schmidt (Box 99)
  - Fritz Hufeld, 1933; Hufeld, Fritz (Box 99)
  - Engros Preis-Verzeichniss, 1902-1903; Mette, Heinr. (Box 99)
  - Trade Catalogue of Vegetable, Flower & Farm Seeds, 1908-1909; Mette, Henry (Box 99)
  - Trade Catalogue of Vegetable, Flower & Farm Seeds, 1924-1925; Mette, Heinr. (Box 99)
  - Wholesale Trade Catalogue of Vegetable, Flower & Farm Seeds, 1929-1930; Mette, Heinr. (Box 99)
  - Wholesale Trade Catalogue of Vegetable, Flower & Farm Seeds, 1935-1936; Mette, Heinrich (Box 99)
  - Annual Trade Seed List, 1902-1903; Putz, Otto (Box 99)
  - Annual Trade Seed List, 1914-1915; Putz, Otto (Box 99)
  - Wholesale Catalogue of Choice German Flower Seeds, 1927-1928; Roemer, Frederick (Box 99)
  - Wholesale Seed-Catalogue, 1913-1914; Sachs, David (Box 99)
  - Albert Schenkel Samenhandlung Exotische Samereien, 1936; Schenkel, Albert (Box 99)
  - Engros-Katalog uber Samen und Pflanzen, 1913-1914; Schenkel, Albert (Box 99)
  - Engros-Catalog, 1903-1904; Schmidt, J.C. (Box 99)
  - Trade Seed Catalogue, 1908; Schmidt, J.C. (Box 99)
  - Preisliste fur den Grosshandel, 1928-1929; Schmidt, J.C. (Box 99)
  - Stechert's Botanical Catalogue, undated; Stechert & Co (Box 99)
    Catalogue No. 85
  - Wholesale Catalogue, undated; Bloemenhof Nurseries (Box 100)
  - Wholesale - Only Dutch Bulbs and Plants, 1914; Grullemans, J.J. & Sons (Box 100)
    59th Edition
  - Wholesale Catalogue, 1951-1952; Ruys, B. Ltd. (Box 100)
  - Wholesale Catalogue of Holland Bulbs and Flower Roots, 1914; Segers Brothers (Box 100)
  - Contract Prices For Delivery After Harvest, 1931; Sluis, Abraham Ltd. (Box 100)
  - Flower Seeds, 1959-1960 Season; Sluis Brothers Ltd. (Box 100)
  - Flower Seeds, 1960-1961 Season; Sluis Brothers Ltd. (Box 100)
  - Flower Seeds, 1959; Sluis, N.V. & Groot (Box 100)
    Crop 1959
  - Novelties and Proved Introductions, 1960; Sluis en Groot (Box 100)
  - Flower Seeds, 1963; Sluis, N.V. & Groot (Box 100)
  - Wholesale Catalogue of Bulbs, 1950 Summer and Autumn; Van Tubergen, C.G. Ltd. (Box 100)
  - Holland Bulbs, 1931; Vanderschoot, John B. Inc. (Box 100)
  - Flower Seeds, 1963; Van Dijk & Co. (Box 100)
  - Catalog, 1932; Van Engelen, A.J. Inc. (Box 100)
  - Wholesale Catalogue of Dutch Flower-Roots, 1915; Van Waveren, M. & Sons, Inc. (Box 100)
  - Transon Brothers & D. Dauvesse's Nurseries: Nursery Trade List 1911-1912, Barbier & Co. (Successors) (Box 101)
  - General Price List, 1907-1908; Dammann & Co. (Box 101)
    No. 166
  - General Price List, 1913-1914; Dammann & Co. (Box 101)
    No. 223
  - Liste des Graines: Seeds of Alpine and Perennial Plants, 1924; Floraire (Box 101)
  - Wholesale List of General Nursey Stock and Roses, 1913 Autumn- 1914 Spring; Gouchault & Turbat Nurseries (Box 101)
  - Wholesale List of General Nursey Stock and Roses, 1915 Autumn- 1916 Spring; Gouchault & Turbat Nurseries (Box 101)
  - Hortus Botanicus Universitatis Asiae Mediae, 1940; Hortus Botanicus (Box 101)
  - Price List, 1914; Lissadell (Box 101)
  - List of Spontaneous Seeds and other Diaspores, 1962; Lund Botanical Garden (Box 101)
  - Wholesale Price List for Seedsmen and Dealers Only, 1913-1914; Honore Roumanille & Fils (Box 101)
  - To the Trade Only Catalogue, 1911; Van Dillewijn & Thiel (Box 101)
  - Vilmorin's Descriptive List, undated; Vilmorin-Andrieux Seed Growers (Box 101)
  - Prix Courant Pour Marchands de Graines de Plantes de Serre Et D'Orangerie, 1920-1921; Vilmorin-Andrieux & Cie. (Box 101)
  - Prix Courant Pour Marchands de Graines de Plantes de Serre Et D'Orangerie, 1921-1922; Vilmorin-Andrieux & Cie. (Box 101)
  - Prix Courant Pour Marchands de Graines D'Arbres Et D'Arbustes, 1924-1925; Vilmorin-Andrieux & Cie. (Box 101)
  - Prix Courant Pour Marchands de Graines de Plantes de Serre Et D'Orangerie, 1927-1928; Vilmorin-Andrieux & Cie. (Box 101)
  - General Wholesale Seedlist, 1928-1929; Vilmorin-Andrieux & Cie. (Box 101)
  - Vilmorin's Seeds: General Wholesale Seedlist, 1930-1931; Vilmorin-Andrieux & Cie. (Box 101)
  - Prix Courant Pour Marchands de Graines D'Arbres Et D'Arbustes, 1931-1932; Vilmorin-Andrieux & Cie. (Box 101)
  - Vilmorin's Seeds, 1933-1934; Vilmorin-Andrieux & Co. (Box 101)
  - Prix Courant Pour Marchands de Graines de Plantes de Serre Et D'Orangerie, 1936-1937; Vilmorin-Andrieux & Cie. (Box 101)
  - Prix Courant Pour Marchands de Graines de Plantes de Serre Et D'Orangerie, 1937-1938; Vilmorin-Andrieux & Cie. (Box 101)
  - Vilmorin's Seeds, 1939; Vilmorin-Andrieux (Box 101)
  - Prix Courant Pour Marchands Grainiers, 1951-1952; Vilmorin-Andrieux (Box 101)
  - Prix Courant Pour Marchands Grainiers, 1954-1955; Vilmorin-Andrieux (Box 101)
  - Hardy Perennial Plants: Season 1963, American Perennial Gardens (Box 102)
  - Hardy Cacti, Colorado Shrubs and Plants, 1901 Spring; Andrews, D.M. (Box 102)
  - Rockmont Nursery, 1915; Andrews, D.M. (Box 102)
  - Rockmont Nursery, 1919; Andrews, D.M. (Box 102)